<resources>


    <string name="app_name">SpiritualGuide</string>

    <!-- Nav Bar -->
    <string name="title_home_tarot">Tarot</string>
    <string name="title_home_quotes">Quotes</string>

    <!-- Mobile Navigation / toolbar titles -->
    <string name="title_toolbar_tarot">TAROT</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_card_meaning">Card Meaning</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_all_cards">All Cards by Arcanas</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_all_readings">All Readings</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_little_cross">The Little Cross</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_simple_path">The Simple Path</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_path_of_wisdom">The Path of Wisdom</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_love_oracle">The Love Oracle</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_little_cross_meaning">Interpretation: Little Cross</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_simple_path_meaning">Interpretation: Simple Path</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_path_of_wisdom_meaning">Interpretation: Path of Wisdom</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_love_oracle_meaning">Interpretation: Love Oracle</string>

    <string name="title_toolbar_quotes">QUOTES</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_qotd">Quote of the Day</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_my_fav_quotes">My Favorite Quotes</string>
    <string name="title_toolbar_fav_options">Options</string>

    <!-- Tarot Home Fragment Bottoms -->
    <string name="cards_home_card_of_day_btn">CARD OF THE DAY</string>
    <string name="cards_home_all_readings_btn">YOUR PERSONAL\nCARD READING</string>
    <string name="cards_home_all_arcanas_btn">ALL CARDS AND\nTHEIR MEANINGS</string>

    <!-- Quotes Home Fragment Buttons -->
    <string name="quotes_home_quote_of_day_btn">QUOTE OF THE DAY</string>
    <string name="quotes_home_my_fav_quotes_btn">MY FAVORITE QUOTES</string>

    <!-- Quotes Options Fragment Buttons -->
    <string name="quotes_options_share_btn">Share</string>
    <string name="quotes_options_delete_btn">Delete from my\nfavorite quotes</string>
    <string name="quotes_options_deleted">Quote DELETED</string>

    <!-- Quotes Fragment Delete-Buttons -->
    <string name="quotes_save_btn">Save in my \nfavorite quotes list</string>

    <!-- All Cards RV Fragment -->
    <string name="allcards_rv_trumps">Major Arcana (Trumps)</string>
    <string name="allcards_rv_cups">Cups (Minor Arcana)</string>
    <string name="allcards_rv_swords">Swords (Minor Arcana)</string>
    <string name="allcards_rv_wands">Wands (Minor Arcana)</string>
    <string name="allcards_rv_coins">Pentacles/Coins (Minor Arcana)</string>

    <!-- Readings Home Fragment -->
    <string name="readings_home_simple_path_tv">The Simple Path</string>
    <string name="readings_home_little_cross_tv">The Little Cross</string>
    <string name="readings_home_path_of_wisdom_tv">The Path of Wisdom</string>
    <string name="readings_home_love_oracle_tv">The Love Oracle</string>

    <!-- Cards readings Buttons -->
    <string name="readings_shuffle_btn">SHUFFLE</string>
    <string name="readings_lay_btn">LAY</string>
    <string name="readings_interpretation_btn">INTERPRETATION</string>

    <!-- Little Cross Fragment -->
    <string name="little_cross_card_1">It\'s\nabout... </string>
    <string name="little_cross_card_2">Don\'t do\nthis! </string>
    <string name="little_cross_card_3">Do this! </string>
    <string name="little_cross_card_4">Future\nsurpise</string>

    <!-- Simple Path Fragment -->
    <string name="simple_path_card_1">Past</string>
    <string name="simple_path_card_2">Present</string>
    <string name="simple_path_card_3">Future</string>

    <!-- Path of Wisdom Fragment -->
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_card_1">Chances</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_card_2_7">objective\nawareness</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_card_3_6">subjective\nemotions</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_card_4_5">reality</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_pic_conscious">CONSCIOUS</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_pic_unconscious">UNCONSCIOUS</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_pic_reality">REALITY</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_pic_past">PAST</string>
    <string name="path_of_wisdom_pic_future">PRESENT</string>

    <!-- Love Oracle Fragment -->
    <string name="love_oracle_card_1">Relation issue</string>
    <string name="love_oracle_card_2">The other\nperson</string>
    <string name="love_oracle_card_3">YOU</string>
    <string name="love_oracle_card_4">What to do</string>

    <!-- One Card Fragment -->
    <string name="one_card_value">Value:</string>
    <string name="one_card_keywords">Keywords</string>
    <string name="one_card_fortune_telling">Fortune telling</string>
    <string name="one_card_meaning">Meaning</string>
    <string name="one_card_qta">Questions to ask</string>
    <string name="one_card_description">Description</string>
    <!-- The Arcanas' names -->
    <string name="major_arcana">Major Arcana</string>
    <string name="minor_cups">Minor Arcana: Cups</string>
    <string name="minor_swords">Minor Arcana: Swords</string>
    <string name="minor_wands">Minor Arcana: Wands</string>
    <string name="minor_coins">Minor Arcana: Coins</string>


    <!-- The Cards -->

    <!-- Major Arcana -->
    <string name="card01_theFool_name">The Fool</string>
    <string name="card01_theFool_keywords">freedom, faith, inexperience, innocence</string>
    <string name="card01_theFool_fortune_telling">Watch for new projects and new beginnings.\nPrepare to take something on faith.\nSomething new comes your way; go for it!</string>
    <string name="card01_theFool_meaning">Freeing yourself from limitation, Expressing joy and youthful vigor, Being open-minded, Taking a leap of faith, Attuning yourself to your instincts, Being eager or curious, Exploring your potential, Embracing innovation and change</string>
    <string name="card01_theFool_qta">What would I do if I felt free to take a leap?\nHow willing am I to be vulnerable and open?\nHow might past experiences help in this new situation?</string>
    <string name="card01_theFool_description">With light step, as if earth and its trammels had little power to restrain him, a young man in gorgeous vestments pauses at the brink of a precipice among the great heights of the world; he surveys the blue distance before him-its expanse of sky rather than the prospect below. His act of eager walking is still indicated, though he is stationary at the given moment; his dog is still bounding. The edge which opens on the depth has no terror; it is as if angels were waiting to uphold him, if it came about that he leaped from the height. His countenance is full of intelligence and expectant dream. He has a rose in one hand and in the other a costly wand, from which depends over his right shoulder a wallet curiously embroidered. He is a prince of the other world on his travels through this one-all amidst the morning glory, in the keen air. The sun, which shines behind him, knows whence he came, whither he is going, and how he will return by another path after many days. He is the spirit in search of experience. Many symbols of the Instituted Mysteries are summarized in this card, which reverses, under high warrants, all the confusions that have preceded it.</string>

    <string name="card02_magician_name">The Magician</string>
    <string name="card02_magician_keywords">capability, empowerment, activity</string>
    <string name="card02_magician_fortune_telling">A powerful man may play a role in your day.\nYour current situation must be seen as one element of a much larger plan.</string>
    <string name="card02_magician_meaning">Taking appropriate action, Receiving guidance from a higher power, Becoming a channel of divine will, Expressing masculine energy in appropriate and constructive ways, Being yourself in every way</string>
    <string name="card02_magician_qta">What am I empowered to do? \nHow might my abilities come into play? \nTo what extent am I making the most of my talents?</string>
    <string name="card02_magician_description">A youthful figure in the robe of a magician, having the countenance of divine Apollo, with smile of confidence and shining eyes. Above his head is the mysterious sign of the Holy Spirit, the sign of life, like an endless cord, forming the figure 8 in a horizontal position . About his waist is a serpent-cincture, the serpent appearing to devour its own tail. This is familiar to most as a conventional symbol of eternity, but here it indicates more especially the eternity of attainment in the spirit. In the Magician\'s right hand is a wand raised towards heaven, while the left hand is pointing to the earth. This dual sign is known in very high grades of the Instituted Mysteries; it shews the descent of grace, virtue and light, drawn from things above and derived to things below. The suggestion throughout is therefore the possession and communication of the Powers and Gifts of the Spirit. On the table in front of the Magician are the symbols of the four Tarot suits, signifying the elements of natural life, which lie like counters before the adept, and he adapts them as he wills. Beneath are roses and lilies, the flos campi and lilium convallium, changed into garden flowers, to shew the culture of aspiration. This card signifies the divine motive in man, reflecting God, the will in the liberation of its union with that which is above. It is also the unity of individual being on all planes, and in a very high sense it is thought, in the fixation thereof. With further reference to what I have called the sign of life and its connexion with the number 8, it may be remembered that Christian Gnosticism speaks of rebirth in Christ as a change "unto the Ogdoad." The mystic number is termed Jerusalem above, the Land flowing with Milk and Honey, the Holy Spirit and the Land of the Lord. According to Martinism, 8 is the number of Christ.</string>

    <string name="card03_high_priestess_name">The High Priestess</string>
    <string name="card03_high_priestess_keywords">intuition, reflection, purity, initiation</string>
    <string name="card03_high_priestess_fortune_telling">A mysterious woman arrives. \nA sexual secret may surface. \nSomeone knows more than he or she will reveal</string>
    <string name="card03_high_priestess_meaning">Listening to your feelings and intuitions, Exploring unconventional spirituality, Keeping secrets, Being receptive, Reflecting instead of acting, Observing others, Preserving purity</string>
    <string name="card03_high_priestess_qta">What might a rebel against tradition do? \nWhat isn\'t being said or revealed? \nWhat could be achieved by observing and reflecting?</string>
    <string name="card03_high_priestess_description">She has the lunar crescent at her feet, a horned diadem on her head, with a globe in the middle place, and a large solar cross on her breast. The scroll in her hands is inscribed with the word Tora, signifying the Greater Law, the Secret Law and the second sense of the Word. It is partly covered by her mantle, to shew that some things are implied and some spoken. She is seated between the white and black pillars - J. and B. - of the mystic Temple, and the veil of the Temple is behind her: it is embroidered with palms and pomegranates. The vestments are flowing and gauzy, and the mantle suggests light-a shimmering radiance. She has been called occult Science on the threshold of the Sanctuary of Isis, but she is really the Secret Church, the House which is of God and man. She represents also the Second Marriage of the Prince who is no longer of this world; she is the spiritual Bride and Mother, the daughter of the stars and the Higher Garden of Eden. She is, in fine, the Queen of the borrowed light, but this is the light of all. She is the Moon nourished by the milk of the Supernal Mother. \nIn a manner, she is also the Supernal Mother herself-that is to say, she is the bright reflection. It is in this sense of reflection that her truest and highest name in bolism is Shekinah-the co-habiting glory. According to Kabalism, there is a Shekinah both above and below. In the superior world it is called Binah, the Supernal Understanding which reflects to the emanations that are beneath. In the lower world it is MaIkuth-that world being, for this purpose, understood as a blessed Kingdom that with which it is made blessed being the Indwelling Glory. Mystically speaking, the Shekinah is the Spiritual Bride of the just man, and when he reads the Law she gives the Divine meaning. There are some respects in which this card is the highest and holiest of the Greater Arcana.</string>

    <string name="card04_empress_name">The Empress</string>
    <string name="card04_empress_keywords">fertility, productivity, ripeness, nurturing</string>
    <string name="card04_empress_fortune_telling">Pregnancy is in the cards. \nAn opportunity to be involved in luxurious sexuality is coming. \nBeware a tendency toward addiction.</string>
    <string name="card04_empress_meaning">Nurturing yourself and others, Bearing fruit, Celebrating your body, Bearing (literal or figurative) children, Reveling in luxury, Mothering those around you in positive ways, Enjoying your sexuality, Getting things done</string>
    <string name="card04_empress_qta">What would a concerned and capable mother do? \nWhat can I do that would emphasize growth? \nHow can I celebrate my own sensuality and sexuality?</string>
    <string name="card04_empress_description">A stately figure, seated, having rich vestments and royal aspect, as of a daughter of heaven and earth. Her diadem is of twelve stars, gathered in a cluster. The symbol of Venus is on the shield which rests near her. A field of corn is ripening in front of her, and beyond there is a fall of water. The sceptre which she bears is surmounted by the globe of this world. She is the inferior Garden of Eden, the Earthly Paradise, all that is symbolized by the visible house of man. She is not Regina coeli, but she is still refugium peccatorum, the fruitful mother of thousands. There are also certain aspects in which she has been correctly described as desire and the wings thereof, as the woman clothed with the sun, as Gloria Mundi and the veil of the Sanctum Sanctorum; but she is not, I may add, the soul that has attained wings, unless all the symbolism is counted up another and unusual way. She is above all things universal fecundity and the outer sense of the Word. This is obvious, because there is no direct message which has been given to man like that which is borne by woman; but she does not herself carry its interpretation. In another order of ideas, the card of the Empress signifies the door or gate by which an entrance is obtained into this life, as into the Garden of Venus; and then the way which leads out therefrom, into that which is beyond, is the secret known to the High Priestess: it is communicated by her to the elect. Most old attributions of this card are completely wrong on the symbolism-as, for example, its identification with the Word, Divine Nature, the Triad, and so forth.</string>

    <string name="card05_emperor_name">The Emperor</string>
    <string name="card05_emperor_keywords">authority, regulation, direction, structure</string>
    <string name="card05_emperor_fortune_telling">A father figure arrives. \nA new employer or authority figure will give you orders. \nExpect discipline or correction in the near future.</string>
    <string name="card05_emperor_meaning">Exercising authority, Defining limits, Directing the flow of work, Communicating clear guidelines, Being in control of yourself and others, Tempering aggressive masculinity with wisdom and experience"</string>
    <string name="card05_emperor_qta">How does the issue of control or regulation impact this situation? \nWhat would a compassionate but strict father do? \nWhat needs more control?</string>
    <string name="card05_emperor_description">He has a form of the Crux Ansata for his sceptre and a globe in his left hand. He is a crowned monarch-commanding, stately, seated on a throne, the arms of which axe fronted by rams\' heads. He is executive and realization, the power of this world, here clothed with the highest of its natural attributes. He is occasionally represented as seated on a cubic stone, which, however, confuses some of the issues. He is the virile power, to which the Empress responds, and in this sense is he who seeks to remove the Veil of Isis; yet she remains Virgo Intacta.\nIt should be understood that this card and that of the Empress do not precisely represent the condition of married life, though this state is implied. On the surface, as I have indicated, they stand for mundane royalty, uplifted on the seats of the mighty; but above this there is the suggestion of another presence. They signify also - and the male figure especially - the higher kingship, occupying the intellectual throne. Hereof is the lordship of thought rather than of the animal world. Both personalities, after their own manner, are \"full of strange experience,\" but theirs is not consciously the wisdom which draws from a higher world. The Emperor has been described as (a) will in its embodied form, but this is only one of its applications, and (b) as an expression of virtualities contained in the Absolute Being-but this is fantasy.</string>

    <string name="card06_hierophant_name">The Hierophant</string>
    <string name="card06_hierophant_keywords">guidance, knowledge, revelation, belief</string>
    <string name="card06_hierophant_fortune_telling">Expect to be caught in a misdeed and punished accordingly. \nPray for forgiveness and confess wrongdoings. \nA more experienced man, spiritual leader, or father figure will come into your life</string>
    <string name="card06_hierophant_meaning">Teaching or guiding others, Searching for the truth, Asking for guidance from a higher power, Acknowledging the wisdom and experience of others, Taking vows, Engaging in heartfelt rituals, Volunteering</string>
    <string name="card06_hierophant_qta">What role might tradition or religion play in this situation? \nWho authored the rules? Who enforces them? Why? \nHow might an experienced guide impact this situation?</string>
    <string name="card06_hierophant_description">He wears the triple crown and is seated between two pillars, but they are not those of the Temple which is guarded by the High Priestess. In his left hand he holds a sceptre terminating in the triple cross, and with his right hand he gives the well-known ecclesiastical sign which is called that of esotericism, distinguishing between the manifest and concealed part of doctrine. It is noticeable in this connexion that the High Priestess makes no sign. At his feet are the crossed keys, and two priestly ministers in albs kneel before him. He has been usually called the Pope, which is a particular application of the more general office that he symbolizes. He is the ruling power of external religion, as the High Priestess is the prevailing genius of the esoteric, withdrawn power. The proper meanings of this card have suffered woeful admixture from nearly all hands. Grand Orient says truly that the Hierophant is the power of the keys, exoteric orthodox doctrine, and the outer side of the life which leads to the doctrine; but he is certainly not the prince of occult doctrine, as another commentator has suggested. He is rather the summa totius theologiæ, when it has passed into the utmost rigidity of expression; but he symbolizes also all things that are righteous and sacred on the manifest side. As such, he is the channel of grace belonging to the world of institution as distinct from that of Nature, and he is the leader of salvation for the human race at large. He is the order and the head of the recognized hierarchy, which is the reflection of another and greater hierarchic order; but it may so happen that the pontiff forgets the significance of this his symbolic state and acts as if he contained within his proper measures all that his sign signifies or his symbol seeks to shew forth. He is not, as it has been thought, philosophy-except on the theological side; he is not inspiration; and he is not religion, although he is a mode of its expression.</string>

    <string name="card07_lovers_name">The Lovers</string>
    <string name="card07_lovers_keywords">love, passion, unity, decision</string>
    <string name="card07_lovers_fortune_telling">A new personal or professional relationship blossoms. \nSexual opportunities abound. \nUnexpectedly, a friend becomes a lover</string>
    <string name="card07_lovers_meaning">Showing your love to others, Expressing passion or romantic feelings, Aligning yourself with groups or like-minded others, Bringing people together, Making well-informed decisions</string>
    <string name="card07_lovers_qta">What guides my choices? \nWhat is my heart leading me to do? \nHow might this decision transform me as a person?</string>
    <string name="card07_lovers_description">The sun shines in the zenith, and beneath is a great winged figure with arms extended, pouring down influences. In the foreground are two human figures, male and female, unveiled before each other, as if Adam and Eve when they first occupied the paradise of the earthly body. Behind the man is the Tree of Life, bearing twelve fruits, and the Tree of the Knowledge of Good and Evil is behind the woman; the serpent is twining round it. The figures suggest youth, virginity, innocence and love before it is contaminated by gross material desire. This is in all simplicity the card of human love, here exhibited as part of the way, the truth and the life. It replaces, by recourse to first principles, the old card of marriage, which I have described previously, and the later follies which depicted man between vice and virtue. In a very high sense, the card is a mystery of the Covenant and Sabbath. The suggestion in respect of the woman is that she signifies that attraction towards the sensitive life which carries within it the idea of the Fall of Man, but she is rather the working of a Secret Law of Providence than a willing and conscious temptress. It is through her imputed lapse that man shall arise ultimately, and only by her can he complete himself. The card is therefore in its way another intimation concerning the great mystery of womanhood. The old meanings fall to pieces of necessity with the old pictures, but even as interpretations of the latter, some of them were of the order of commonplace and others were false in symbolism.</string>

    <string name="card08_chariot_name">The Chariot</string>
    <string name="card08_chariot_keywords">advancement, victory, triumph, success</string>
    <string name="card08_chariot_fortune_telling">Victory is a certainty. \nMove ahead with all plans. \nBeware the jealousy of others.</string>
    <string name="card08_chariot_meaning">Breaking through barriers, Moving forward with confidence and authority, Reaching the pinnacle of success, Basking in the glory of achievement, Guiding an effort to total victory, Establishing yourself as a worthy leader</string>
    <string name="card08_chariot_qta">To what extent have I arrived? What will my next challenge be? \nHow can I use past achievements to their best advantage? \nWhat would the criteria for real and meaningful success be?</string>
    <string name="card08_chariot_description">An erect and princely figure carrying a drawn sword and corresponding, broadly speaking, to the traditional description which I have given in the first part. On the shoulders of the victorious hero are supposed to be the Urim and Thummim. He has led captivity captive; he is conquest on all planes - in the mind, in science, in progress, in certain trials of initiation. He has thus replied to the sphinx, and it is on this account that I have accepted the variation of Éliphas Lévi; two sphinxes thus draw his chariot. He is above all things triumph in the mind. \nIt is to be understood for this reason a) that the question of the sphinx is concerned with a Mystery of Nature and not of the world of Grace, to which the charioteer could offer no answer; b) that the planes of his conquest are manifest or external and not within himself; c) that the liberation which he effects may leave himself in the bondage of the logical understanding; d) that the tests of initiation through which he has passed in triumph are to be understood physically or rationally; and (e) that if he came to the pillars of that Temple between which the High Priestess is seated, he could not open the scroll called Tora, nor if she questioned him could he answer. He is not hereditary royalty and he is not priesthood.</string>

    <string name="card09_strength_name">The Strength</string>
    <string name="card09_strength_keywords">discipline, boldness, self-discipline, power, vitality</string>
    <string name="card09_strength_fortune_telling">Your self-control will be tested. \nA woman will seek to change her partner or lover. \nYou are a strong, capable person.</string>
    <string name="card09_strength_meaning">Imposing restrictions on yourself for your own benefit, Bringing your passions under the control of reason, Resisting impulses that work against your best interests, Taking bold action</string>
    <string name="card09_strength_qta">To what extent is your life (or work) balanced? \nHow can you achieve greater objectivity? \nWhat course of action would be fair to everyone concerned?</string>
    <string name="card09_strength_description">A woman, over whose head there broods the same symbol of life which we have seen in the card of the Magician, is closing the jaws of a lion. The only point in which this design differs from the conventional presentations is that her beneficent fortitude has already subdued the lion, which is being led by a chain of flowers. For reasons which satisfy myself, this card has been interchanged with that of justice, which is usually numbered eight. As the variation carries nothing with it which will signify to the reader, there is no cause for explanation. Fortitude, in one of its most exalted aspects, is connected with the Divine Mystery of Union; the virtue, of course, operates in all planes, and hence draws on all in its symbolism. It connects also with innocentia inviolata, and with the strength which resides in contemplation.
These higher meanings are, however, matters of inference, and I do not suggest that they are transparent on the surface of the card. They are intimated in a concealed manner by the chain of flowers, which signifies, among many other things, the sweet yoke and the light burden of Divine Law, when it has been taken into the heart of hearts. The card has nothing to do with self-confidence in the ordinary sense, though this has been suggested-but it concerns the confidence of those whose strength is God, who have found their refuge in Him. There is one aspect in which the lion signifies the passions, and she who is called Strength is the higher nature in its liberation. It has walked upon the asp and the basilisk and has trodden down the lion and the dragon.
    </string>


    <!-- CUPS -->
    <!-- WANDS -->
    <!-- SWORDS -->
    <!-- COINS -->

</resources>